<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss
  version="2.0"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/">
  <channel>
    <title>Dilettante Dad</title>
    <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dilettante Dad</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:33:04 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>Mid July Weekend</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/mid-july-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 09:33:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/mid-july-weekend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;fun-filled-week-in-july&#34;&gt;Fun filled Week in July&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This week was busy but fun. On Wednesday, July 9 Kari, Grant, Truman, and I all took the GO train out to Exhibition to see Weird Al Yankovic at Budweiser Gardens. It was the boys&amp;rsquo; first concert. They were excited, but apprehensive. I was a little concerned as it started to rain, but what is an outdoor concert without a little rain. We followed the crowd of people through the parking lot for BMO field, over the foot bridge that crosses Lakeshore blvd to the grounds of Budweiser Gardens. As we approached the gates I saw a familiar face - Kari&amp;rsquo;s cousin&amp;rsquo;s husband Ricky. I shouted &amp;ldquo;Ricky, Ricky&amp;rdquo; into the crowd. He turned and said &amp;lsquo;Not Ricky, Andy. Do I know you?&amp;quot;. Ricky has a twin named Andy. We told him how we knew Ricky, and we went off to our respective seats.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item>
      <title>Canada Day</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/canada-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:40:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/canada-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tuesday, July 1st was Canada Day. Kari, Grant, Truman and I were able to go to the Blue Jays game. Kari&amp;rsquo;s dad often gets tickets to sporting events, and he generously will offer them to us. So once a year we find ourselves at a Blue Jays game. Last year was Father&amp;rsquo;s Day and this year was Canada Day. The Blue Jays were playing the Yankees, which is always an exciting matchup. Aaron Judge #99 for the Yankees is widely regarded to be one of the best players in the world right now, so we were excited to go see him play.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item>
      <title>Vacation</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 11:09:56 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/vacation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;vacation-on-the-adriatic-sea&#34;&gt;Vacation on the Adriatic Sea&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Friday May 16th we embarked on a family trip to Italy and Croatia. This is a trip Kari and I had been mulling over since before the boys were born. The plan: To fly to Venice - spend a few days there, then take a ferry across the Adriatic to Croatia, and spend a week on the Dalmatian coast.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The flight was delayed and long, but direct from Toronto to Venice. We sat two by two Kari with Grant, myself and Truman the row behind them. We were fortunate that we all got some sleep.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item>
      <title>Retreat</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/retreat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:39:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/retreat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;retreat&#34;&gt;Retreat&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The plan for this past week was to fly to the US for a work retreat. These types of forced interactions always make me nervous. An unprecedented snow fall and a plane crash at YYZ, meant my flight was cancelled. While it was stressful having my travel plans up in the air, I was grateful as it meant I got to spend Family Day with my family as opposed to a bunch of strangers who happen to share the same employer. We spent the day 5 pin bowling with Jeremy, Simon and Jess at a shopping mall in Scarborough, kids in one lane and adults in the adjacent one.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item>
      <title>Snow Day</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/snowday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 10:26:50 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/snowday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;team-brothers-snow-day&#34;&gt;Team Brothers: Snow Day&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a week that would normally have been dominated by Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day and a P.A. day on Friday, our schedule was upended by the largest single snow fall we have had in years. The snow started on Wednesday afternoon, and did not stop until Thursday morning. The first casualty was Grant&amp;rsquo;s Wednesday evening soccer practice. Next was school on Thursday, and finally Kari&amp;rsquo;s office closed too.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item>
      <title>Hitting the Slopes</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/skiing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:06:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/skiing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hitting-the-slopes&#34;&gt;Hitting the Slopes&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today we decided to forgo our regularly scheduled Saturday activities and take the boys skiing. While the Greater-Toronto-Area is not known for its mountainous terrain, there are several small ski hills within an hours drive of the city. We chose to go to a ski park on the Niagara escarpment called Glen Eden in Milton, where I grew up, and where I spent many evenings skiing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The original plan had been that I would have taken Grant, and Truman would have stayed home with Kari. This caused Truman to get very upset. Kari offered to come and so that I would not have to supervise two children on the &amp;ldquo;mountain&amp;rdquo;, but she was not exactly thrilled with the idea of skiing. She did not grow up skiing, she had been exactly once and never felt in control going down the hill.&#xA;To add to her reservations, we had been unable to secure rentals or lessons beforehand. We had been instructed to call Glen Eden the day of our desired outing to see if rentals and lessons would be available. This is the type of non-formalized plan that makes Kari uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/helloworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:53:34 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ianmcgonigle.github.io/dilettantedad.github.io/posts/helloworld/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-has-been-a-long-time-comming&#34;&gt;This has been a long time comming&amp;hellip;.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many reasons for me to start writing in something like a journal. As I get older my memory does not serve me as well as it used to. Writing down what happened, who was involved, and how I felt about it, will help me forge stronger memories in the first place, as well function as a reference I can look back on in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel>
</rss>
